The Register to the Betsy Jolas Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Correspondence, 1937-2010; Series II
  - Paper, 1
    - The National Institute of Arts and Letters
      See American Academy of Arts and Letters
    - National Music Museum, 1988-1989; 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - National Symphony Orchestra, 1996; 3 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Nectoux, Jean-Michel, 1996-1998; 7 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      See also Musée d'Orsay; Radio France
    - Nelson, Erika, 2003; 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Nelson, Philip F., 1977-1983; 6 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Nemko, Deborah, 1998; 4 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Neriz, Maurice, 1975; 2 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Network for New Music, 1996; 4 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Neuberger, Roberto Pablo, 1990; 3 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Newband
      See Drummond, Dean
    - New England Conservatory, 1992-1993; 4 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - New Music Concerts (Toronto), 1975-1976; 5 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - New Music Consort, 1978; 2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - New Opera Theatre (Brooklyn Academy of Music), 1977-1978; 10 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      See also Eastman, Ursula
    - New York Kantorei
      See Theodore Presser Company
    - New York Philharmonic, 1984; 4 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      See also Druckman, Jacob
    - New York Public Library, No date; 5 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Nichols, Roger, 1996-1999; 4 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - ?, Nicolas, 1996; 2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Nicolas, François, 1987-1990, no date; 8 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Nicout, Jacques, 1973; 1 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Nienstedt, Dörte, 1989; 2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Niepce, Janine, 1980; 2 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Nies, Christel, 2002-2005; 3 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Nigg, Serge, 1988-1990; 5 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      See also Les Percussions de Strasbourg
    - Nin-Culmell, Joaquin, 1979; 1 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Noble, Jeremy, 1984-1985, no date; 4 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      See also University at Buffalo, SUNY
    - Nobre, Marlos, 1984-1985; 5 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Noël, Béatrice, 1998; 2 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - ?, Nola [Masse?], No date; 1 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Nonat, Alain, 1974; 1 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Nono, Luigi, 1963, no date; 3 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Norddeutscher Rundfunk (NDR), 1968; 1 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Norfolk Chamber Music Festival, 1992-1994; 2 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      See also Theodore Presser Company; Yale University
    - Nørgård, Per, 1990; 2 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Notter, Annette, 1984; 4 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Noufflard, Geneviève, 1985; 1 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Nouri, Gwenaëlle, 1993; 1 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Novello Company, 1974; 1 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Nunes, Emmanuel, 1986; 1 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Nuovi Spazi Sonori, 1988-1991; 4 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Ockenden, Rebecca, 2000; 1 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Octobre en Normandie, 2001; 2 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Octuor de Paris, 1971; 1 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Ohana, Maurice, 1974; 2 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Oleg, Raphael, No date; 5 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Olivier, Philippe, 1991-1992; 7 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Olsen, Louise and Paul Rovsing, 1981; 1 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Opéra de Lyon, 1981 [?]-1995; 17 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      See also Brossman, Jean-Pierre; Éditions Salabert; Erlo, Louis; Lainé Galodé, Catherine; Nagano, Kent
    - Opera de Nederlandse Operastichting, 1976; 2 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Opéra (National) de Paris, 1983-1995; 3 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      See also Liebermann, Rolf
    - Opéra de Paris - Bastille, 1990; 1 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Opéra du Rhin, 1973; 3 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - d'Un Opera de Voyage (Piece), 2002; 14 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      See also Alphonse Leduc Éditeurs; Bon, André; Cohen-Levinas, Danielle; Grés, Lydia; Kiesgen, Camile; Labie, Jean-François; Leguay, Laetitia
    - Opera-Studio, 1973; 2 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Orchestre de Besançon, 1995-1997; 4 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Orchestre de Paris
      See Dutilleux, Henri
    - Orchestre National Bordeaux Aquitaine
      See Lombard, Alain
    - Orchestra Sinfonica dell'Emilia-Romagna "Arturo Toscanini", 1979; 1 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - L'Ordre National du Mérite, 1980-1981; 8 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - L'Oreille en Fête, 1991; 1 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Organisation pour les Recherches et l'Enseignement de la Musique (OREM)
      See Andreani, Eveline; Institut Française
    - Ostendorf, John, No date; 1 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Österreichische Gesellschaft für Musik, 1968; 4 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Ouzounoff, Alexandre, 1984; 1 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Overbeck, Lois, 1991-2000; 2 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Pablo, Luis de, 1967-2010; 13 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Packer, Randall, No date; 1 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Page, Tim, 1996; 4 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Painter, Karen, 2001; 1 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Palmer, Muriel C., 1994; 2 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Pan, Younghi, 1993; 1 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - de Panafieu, Mme, 1988; 2 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Panitsa, Yvonne, 1997; 2 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Parcells, Elizabeth (Betsy), 1977-1996; 5 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Parc de la Villette, 1984-1988; 8 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Pareille, Paul, No date; 1 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - The Paris New Music Review
      See Livingston, Guy
    - Paris, Ville de (Mairie, Police, etc.), 1981-2001; 25 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      See also Légion d'Honneur
    - Park Lane Group, 1973; 3 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Parker, Deborah
    - Parrenin, Jacques, 1959; 1 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Pathé Marconi, 1969; 2 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      See also Lanceron, Alain; Leduc, Jean
    - Patterson, Paul, 1984; 1 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Paulu, Burton, 1976; 3 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Pauly-Laubry, Henri, 1994; 2 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Peabody Institute, 1982; 1 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Pearlman, Martin, 1992; 1 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Pécou, Thierry, 1993; 2 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Pecquet, Frank, 1991; 2 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Peignois, Béatrice, 1997; 1 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - La Péniche Opera, 2001, no date; 6 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Peraud, Pascal, 1987; 3 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Les Percussions des Strasbourg, 1968, no date; 4 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      See also Nigg, Serge; Shamir, Igal
    - Perdigon, Pierre, 1987; 2 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Périer, Alain, 1977; 1 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Perlis, Vivian (and Sandy), 1973-2008, no date; 76 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      See also Éditions Salabert; Theodore Presser Company; Wajyma, Hiroko
    - Persichetti, Vincent
    - Personnalité de l'Année, 1992-1993, no date; 7 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Perspectives of New Music, 1984; 1 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Pesson, Gérard, 1986-2009, no date; 52 (Box 34, Folder 11)
      See also D'un Opéra de Voyage; Société des Auteurs, Compositeurs, et Éditeurs de Musique
    - Petit, Arnaud, 1991; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Petit, Jean-Louis, 1973-1983; 11 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Peyser, Joan, 1973; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Philharmonia Orchestra, 1993-1994; 2 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - ?, Philippe and Carmen, 1974; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Philippe, Laurent, 1988 [?]; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Philips, 1970; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Picard, Claude, 2006; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Picard, Roger, No date; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Picon, Geneviève, 1974; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Pierrakos, Hélène, 1995; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Pierre, Loïc, No date; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Pigeaud, François, 1974-1984; 8 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Pillsbury, Henry, 1987-2001; 3 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Pincherle, Marc, 1970; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Pinon, Gerard, No date; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Pirat, Cécile, 1997; 2 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Pisar, Judith, 1989-1994; 3 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Pisati, Maurizio, 1989; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Pizet, Anne, 1986; 1 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Plantamura, Carol, 1977-1999; 29 (Box 34, Folder 13)
      See also University of California San Diego
    - Pochon, Virginie, 2007; 1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Poindefert, Bruno, 1991; 2 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Poirier, Alain, 1995-2005; 4 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Polskie Wydawnictwo Muzyczne (PWM), 1963-1974; 13 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Poole, John, 1992-2002, no date; 3 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Popelard, Marie-Hélène, 2001; 1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Porada, Ingo, 1990-1993; 15 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Porcile, François, 1975; 3 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Post, Nora, 1983-1986; 15 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Postraine, François, 1995; 1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Potocki, Christophe, 1996; 1 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Pousseur, Henri, 1980-1985; 8 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Pozzi, Raffaele
      See Campus Internazionale di Musica
    - Pradourat, Christian, 1978; 2 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Prappote, Anne, No date; 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Préfet de la Région Alsace, 2001; 2 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Présidence de la République (France), 1992; 3 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      See also Adler, Laure; Chirac, Jacques; Giscard d'Estaing, Valery; Mitterrand, François
    - Prevost, Germain, 1968-1969; 4 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Premier Ministre (Denmark), 1985; 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Premier Ministre (France), 1984; 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Priestman, Katherine, 2000-2001; 3 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Prin, Yves, 1995-2001; 2 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Printemps des Arts de Monte-Carlo, 2004; 4 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Pro Lyrica, 1991; 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Prodromidès, Jean, 1989; 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Protonotarios, Maria, 1993; 2 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Pruett, James
      See Library of Congress
    - Puchala, Veronique, 2006; 1 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Quatuor Leonore, 1993; 5 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Quatuor Ludwig, No date; 1 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Quéré, France, 1982-1995; 5 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Quéré, Yves, 1998-2007, no date; 43 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Quinon, René, 2000; 5 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Quintard, Marc-Henri, 1978; 1 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Racot, Gilles, 1990-1999; 5 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Radio Classique, 2005; 4 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Radio Courtoisie, 1995; 1 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Radiodiffusion-Télévision Française (RTF; ORTF), 1950-1983 [?]; 50 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      See also Dutilleux, Henri; Hasquenoph, Pierre; Radio France
    - Radio France, 1976-2006; 27 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      See also Armengaud, Jean Pierre; Cantagrel, Gilles; Chaynes, Charles; Derrien, Jean-Pierre; Éditions Salabert; Erisman, Guy; Haguenauer, Jean-Louis; Hasquenoph, Pierre; Koering, René; Radiodiffusion-Télévision Française; Samuel, Claude
    - Radio Suisse Romande (SSR), 1966-2001; 3 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Radio Telefís Éirann (RTE), 1978; 2 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Radio Télévision Belge, 1972; 1 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      See also Deliège, Célestin
    - Radio-Télévision Grecque, 1993; 1 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Rahn, John
      See Perspectives of New Music
    - Raibaldi, Martine, 1991; 2 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Prince Rainier III (of Monaco)
      See Monaco, Principauté de
    - Ramaut, Alban, 1996-2001; 15 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Ramey, Phillip, 1984; 1 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Ramiro, Conceptio, 1988; 1 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Rands, Bernard, 1977-2003; 15 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      See also Crumb, George; Theodore Presser Company; University of California, San Diego; Wajyma, Hiroko
    - Range, Ulrike, 2000-2004; 11 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Rangne, Philip, 1984; 1 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - The Raschèr Saxophone Quartet, 1984, no date; 2 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Raverdy, Philippe, 1997-2005; 2 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Rayer, Philippe, 1990; 2 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Reboul, Olivier, 2000; 1 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Reffait, Jean-Dominique, 2007; 1 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Reibel, Guy, 1982; 1 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Reichel, Alicia, 1969-1970; 18 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Reimann, Aribert, 1999-2005; 4 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Rémoud, A.C., No date; 2 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Renard, Delphine, No date; 2 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Renaud, Jeanne
      See Le Groupe de la Place Royale
    - Renault, Olivier, 1991; 1 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Rencontres Contemporaines de St. Privat d'Allier, 1999; 3 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Rencontres d'Ensembles de Violoncelles de Beauvais, 1998; 1 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Rencontres Internationales d'Art Contemporain, 1975; 4 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Rencontres Internationales de Genève, 1975; 5 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Rencontre National Contre L'Apartheid, 1991; 1 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Le Républicain Lorrain, 1986-1998; 2 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Ress, Paul, 1987 [?]; 3 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Restaurant du Parc, 1999; 1 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Retzel, Frank, 1976; 4 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Reverdy, Michèle, No date; 8 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Reverdy, Pierre, 1949-2009; 10 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Reynolds, Roger
    - Rhodes, Samuel, 1992; 3 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Ribeiro-Pereira, José Miguel, 1984; 2 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Richardson, Lucy, 1997; 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Ricou, Claude
      See Les Percussions des Strasbourg
    - Ridés, Michèle, 1991; 2 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Riemann Musiklexikon
      See B. Schott's Söhne
    - Rieunier, Françoise, 1979; 6 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Rieunier, Jean-Paul, 1987; 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Riou, Laurent, 1978-1995; 14 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Ripley, Colette S., 1992; 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Rist, Simone, 1967; 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Ritzenthaler, Claude, 2002; 6 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Rivalland, Françoise, 2004-2005; 3 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Rivière, Jean-Pierre, 1980; 2 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Robert, Martial, 1987; 2 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Roberts, Gladys, 1973; 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Robet, C., Dr., 1994; 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - The Rockefeller Foundation
    - Rockwell, Svetlana, 1985-1998; 7 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Roissard, Pierre, 1985; 2 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Ronzon, Laurent, 1996; 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Rophe, Pascal, 1988; 1 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Rorem, Ned, 1984-1986; 4 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Rose, Gil, 1998; 6 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rosen, Judith and Ronald S., 1972; 2 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rosenberg-Sinclair, Micheline, 2000; 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rosenboom, David, 1991; 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rosenfeld, Jayn, 1988; 2 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rosenthal, Manuel, 1993; 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rosoor, Caroline, 1992; 2 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Ross, Edward Hunter, 1981; 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Roth, Victoria, 1983; 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rothman, Daniel, 1983-1986; 3 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rotily, Jocelyne, 2002; 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Roubos, Robert
      See Southern Illinois University at Carbondale
    - Rousseau, Jean-Pierre
      See Radio France
    - Rousseau-Dujardin, Jacqueline, 2001; 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Roussel, Léonard, 2006; 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - de Rouville, Henry, 1980; 2 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Roy, Madeleine
      See Bernède, Jean-Claude
    - Royal Academy of Music (Royal College)
      See Patterson, Paul
    - Rubin, Martina, 1982; 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rue, Beth and George, 1991; 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rumold, Rainer, 1994-2002; 16 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Rychen, Sara, 1997; 1 (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Sacawa, Brian, 2003; 1 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Sacher, Paul
    - Sadie, Stanley
      See Grove Dictionary of Music
    - Safar, Roula, 1999; 2 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Sage City Symphony, 1973; 1 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Sahbaï, Iradj, 1999; 1 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - St. James Press, 1990, no date; 4 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Sakkas, Spiros
    - Salem, Daniel, 1996; 1 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Salib, Mark, 1988; 1 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Salvador, Josefina, 1974; 2 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Salzmann, Edith
      See Corda Quartett
    - Sampen, John, 1993; 2 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Samuel, Claude, 1975-2000; 15 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Santos Salas, José Antonio, 2002; 1 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Sarko, Albert, 1978; 5 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Sauvage, Camille
      See L'Ordre National du Mérite
    - Schachter, Daniel, 1992; 2 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Scheib, Amei
      See Arbeit und Kultur Saarland GmbH
    - Scherchen, Tona, 1964-1992; 8 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      See also Milhaud, Darius
    - Schlieman, John, 1999; 1 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Schmidt, André, 1995; 5 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      See also Levy, Jacqueline
    - Schmitz, Johannes, 1985; 2 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Schober, Brian, 1975-1987, no date; 7 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Schoeller, Philippe, 1991; 1 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Schoendorff, Denise and Rémi, 1995; 3 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Schroeder, Marianne, 1987-1991; 3 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Schuller, Gunther, 1975-2009; 12 (Box 35, Folder 11)
      See also Fromm, Paul
    - Schultz, Thomas, 1992-1993; 4 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Schwann Publications, 1998; 1 (Box 35, Folder 12)
      See also Schwann, William
    - Schwann, William, 1986; 5 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Schweizer Radio DRS2, 2004; 4 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Sciama, Guillame, 1987; 1 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - SDA Productions (Canada), 1998; 1 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Le Secrétaire d'Etat - France (Various), 1975-1976; 10 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Sekely, Rachel, 2000; 1 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Sellars, James
      See Hartt School of Music
    - Semaines Musicales Ínternationales de Paris
      See de Lavigne, Jean-Pierre
    - Sergent, Jean-Jacques, 1987; 1 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Serre, Catherine, 1994; 1 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Serrou, Bruno, 1991; 1 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Service, Tom, 1996; 3 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Serviere, Antonin, 2000; 5 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Shailor, Barbara A., 2002; 2 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shamir, Igal and Nicole, 1986; 3 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shams, Jonathan, 1991; 1 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shank, Ted, 1991; 1 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shapiro, Judith (wife of Jay Shapiro), 1970-1984; 10 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Sharpley, John, 1988; 7 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shattenkirk, Ray, 1982; 4 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shaw, Julian, 1997; 1 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shelemay, Kay Kaufman, 1997-1998; 3 (Box 35, Folder 13)
      See also Harvard University
    - Shelley, Sally Swing, 1995-2001, no date; 5 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shelton, Lucy, 2000-2001; 3 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Sheng, Bright, 1988; 2 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shenton, Andrew, 1996; 1 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shimizu, Ken, 1987; 2 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Shreveport Symphony
      See Deutsch, Margery
    - Siegel, Martha, 1972; 4 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Sierra, Arlene, 1994; 1 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Sigers, Karen, 1991; 1 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Sills, David L., 1988; 2 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Simms, Bryan
    - Simmons, Nina, 1993-1995; 3 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Simonds, Caroline, 1969-2002; 10 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      See also Brant, Henry
    - Simonet, Christophe, 2002; 2 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Simpson, David, 2003; 1 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      See also Mouffetard, Nouveau Theatre
    - Sine Qua Non
      See Bousch, François
    - Singier, Jean-Marc, 1997, no date; 2 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Singelbach, Barbara, 1973; 2 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Sirguey, Gait, 1996; 2 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Siwe, Thomas, 1996; 1 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Slatkin, Leonard
      See National Symphony Orchestra
    - Sloane, Ethan
      See Boston University
    - Smadja, Marguerite, 1986; 2 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Gary, 2000-2001; 3 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Gregg, 1975-2001; 4 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Smith, Leland, 1977; 1 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Smith, William Jay, 2004; 5 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Snowman, N., 1976; 2 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Sobel, Bernard, 1997-2002; 5 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      See also Dufour, Jean
    - Société des Auteurs, Compositeurs, et Éditeurs de Musique (SACEM), 1975-1992; 7 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      See also Artaud, Pierre-Yves; Contet, Henri; Derrien, Jean-Pierre; L'Ordre National du Mérite; Tournier, Jean-Loup
    - Société des Auteurs et Compositeurs Dramatiques (SACD), 1975-2003, no date; 16 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      See also L'Ordre National du Mérite
    - Société Civile pour l'Administration des Droits des Artistes et Musiciens Interprètes (ADAMI), 1996; 1 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Société des Concerts du Conservatoire de Chambéry, 1976; 1 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Société d'Editions Radio-Phono (SERP), 1976; 1 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Société Franz Schubert (SFS), 1992; 1 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Société Francaise d'Analyse Musicale (SFAM), 1989-1990; 5 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Société Française Schneider Radio-Télévision, 1969; 3 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Société Internationale pour la Musique Contemporaine, 1993-1994; 3 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Société de Musique de Chambre de Lyon, 2002; 7 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      See also Levin, Robert; Kashkashian, Kim
    - Société Musicale René Herbin, 1992; 1 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Société National de Musique, 1950; 1 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Sollins-Brown, Susan, 2002; 2 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Solomon, Nicolette, 1987; 1 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Solveen, Marthe (Wife of Henri Solveen), 1997-1999; 3 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Son, Yung-Wha, 1984-1986; 3 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Soper, Hélène (née Jolas - cousin; duaghter of Jacques), 1983-2005; 7 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Soskin, Eileen, 1981; 2 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Soulier, Mr., 1990; 1 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Soullière, Anne-Marie, 1980-2000, no date; 32 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Souris, Albert and Fifi, 1998 [?]; 1 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Southern Illinois University at Carbondale, 1987; 2 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Sowerwine, Charles "Chips", 1989; 1 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Spahiu, Besa, 1991; 2 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Spanier, Sandra, 1992; 1 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Sparnaay, Harry, 1985; 10 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Sprigge, Elizabeth, 1958; 1 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Stadt Darmstadt Internationales Musikinstitut, 1969; 2 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Staley, Thomas F., 1988; 1 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Stavy, Nicolas, 1998; 1 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Stein, Leonard, 1964-1996; 19 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      See also Schultz, Thomas
    - Steinberg, Michael, No date; 1 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Steinitz, Richard, 1995-1998; 8 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Stemper, Frank, 1982-1987; 6 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Stétié, Salah, 1968; 2 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Stevens, Claudia, 1982-1987; 9 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Stevens, Delores, 1984; 1 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Stichweh, Klaus, 1980-1987; 4 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Stiegler, Dominique, 2005; 1 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Stock, David, 1977; 1 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Stockhausen, Karlheinz, 1972; 35 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Stockhausen, Markus, 2007; 1 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Stone, Julie, 1988; 3 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Stoop, Paul, 2002-2003; 2 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Stoyanovich, Patrick, 1988; 1 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Strasfogel, Ian
      See Eastman, Ursula; New Opera Theatre (Brooklyn Academy of Music)
    - Strizich, Robert, 1997; 2 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Strobel, Heinrich, 1957-1970; 5 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Studio de Musique Contemporaine (SMC), 1963-1964; 5 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      See also Guyonnet, Jacques
    - Sublett, Virginia, 1993; 2 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Sub-Stance Journal, 1987; 1 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Südwestfunk Baden-Baden, 1969-1971; 6 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      See also Baruch, Gerth-Wolfgang; Strobel, Heinrich
    - Summerfield, Susan, 1986; 1 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Summers, William John
      See Dartmouth College; Theodore Presser Company
    - Surrans, Alain, 1988-2002; 3 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Suter, Jean-François, 1971; 2 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Swarthmore College
      See Theodore Presser Company; Swing, Peter Gram
    - Swedensky, Linda, 1990; 3 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Swing, Peter Gram, 1976-1978; 5 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Syndicat National de l'Edition Phonographique et Audiovisuelle (SNEPA), 1977; 5 (Box 36, Folder 7)